[
    {
      "question": "Le temps est ______.",
      "answer": "inéluctable",
      "options": ["inéluctable", "époustouflant", "sérendipité", "procrastiner"]
    },
    {
      "question": "La vue est ______.",
      "answer": "époustouflante",
      "options": ["époustouflante", "lugubre", "pusillanime", "anachronisme"]
    },
    {
      "question": "C’était de la ______.",
      "answer": "sérendipité",
      "options": ["sérendipité", "fulgurant", "hypnagogique", "obséquieux"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Il ______ toujours.",
      "answer": "procrastine",
      "options": ["procrastine", "regarde", "joue", "pense"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Sa carrière est ______.",
      "answer": "fulgurante",
      "options": ["fulgurante", "inéluctable", "sérendipité", "obséquieux"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Le ciel est ______.",
      "answer": "lugubre",
      "options": ["lugubre", "fatigué", "content", "anachronisme"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Il est ______.",
      "answer": "pusillanime",
      "options": ["pusillanime", "procrastine", "joue", "mange"]
    },
    {
      "question": "C’est un ______.",
      "answer": "anachronisme",
      "options": ["anachronisme", "hypnagogique", "inéluctable", "sérendipité"]
    },
    {
      "question": "C’est un rêve ______.",
      "answer": "hypnagogique",
      "options": ["hypnagogique", "sérendipité", "époustouflant", "fatigué"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Il est ______.",
      "answer": "obséquieux",
      "options": ["obséquieux", "inéluctable", "content", "regarde"]
    }
  ]
  